3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ideas
6 WORDTAG O mind
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ EDT
5 WORDTAG O 416
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ round-the-clock
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-129
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ operators
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Western
16 WORDTAG O event
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Raju
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ lounge
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Moore
6 WORDTAG O briefing
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
9 WORDTAG O maybe
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ floor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ATLETICO
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wenatchee
13 WORDTAG O 82
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Blijlevens
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marubeni
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bradley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ REWARDS
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ chilli
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ institute
6 WORDTAG O mate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 44.3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Haruchika
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lie
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Joulwan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pre-election
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lenzing
12 WORDTAG O cow
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Suedwest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ well-to-do
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ organist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rationalised
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Issuer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ STAR
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fund
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 31,347
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ .357
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9.0-12.0
5 WORDTAG O showers
7 WORDTAG O prix
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ shouted
9 WORDTAG O reduce
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tax-exempt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pre-abnormals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-mth
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ weighted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ burial
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Taibe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ detainees
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grasu
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Named
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tetouan
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ inspection
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ contains
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zambian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ disturbances
61 WORDTAG O run
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SWP
10 WORDTAG O clocked
36 WORDTAG O wickets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 17-0-91-0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lesser
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cacic
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ disguised
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ takings
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ uncertainty
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ slammed
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ meningitis
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ piped
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ academic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bestop
35 WORDTAG O started
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ embassies
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ redeemed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2,891.00
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3rd
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ SALES
21 WORDTAG O drugs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Milenko
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chairmen
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aleksander
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ retaliated
80 WORDTAG O during
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ includind
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zarins
84 WORDTAG O still
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BP
716 WORDTAG O by
8 WORDTAG O FORECAST
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ indignant
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Talks
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ eliminate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-1-24-3
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rajavi
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ responsibility
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ GETS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 66-14
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ajay
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rayyan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ knelt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 205-9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shape
10 WORDTAG O suffering
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ steel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MEXICAN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ villagers
16 WORDTAG O 10,000
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ predictions
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ associate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chevron
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sport
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hoffman
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Riza
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 637.50
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ safeguarded
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ definitive
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ CALCUTTA
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rokmeier
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ adoring
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ opium
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-for-4
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
1 WORDTAG I-MISC News
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wim
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CONGO
16 WORDTAG O walked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aitken
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ decomposed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Funds
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ .359
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ illustrious
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ happy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unrelated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ marine
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ determining
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
53 WORDTAG O security
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ businesslike
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5.24
27 WORDTAG O violence
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hitleresque
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ trains
392 WORDTAG O 5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Clerq
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ball
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 97.80
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ discontinued
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ decrees
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Anthuan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yap
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northampton
9 WORDTAG O scientific
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dev
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 502
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Islamabad
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sierra
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
12 WORDTAG O history
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Glenwood
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ combined
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ tracks
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aegon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 82-0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sun-baked
17 WORDTAG O thought
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pang
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inchon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 92.0-94.5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10.8
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Borrego
15 WORDTAG O published
1 WORDTAG O Medical
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hassania
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ co-producer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ minimium
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Xhelili
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 21,228.80
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jornada
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zuleeg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Muralidaran
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ reference
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ British-based
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 78th
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rig
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ grace
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nine-year-old
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sahara
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 65.61
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7.84
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ time-trial
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ wine
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 255-9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8:12.04
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fluminense
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ JV
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KATHIMERINI
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ introduce
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ networked
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ anywhere
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ indifference
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shinichi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ misleading
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Schork
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 864148
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ S.C.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Howe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ insist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vow
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ evasion
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Carbonell
46 WORDTAG O ahead
1 WORDTAG I-ORG HONG
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kabul
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Shanghai
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ arbitrage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mohajir
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ upturn
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jerry
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 50.250
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7.50
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Coppinger
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7706
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ flows
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pro-Baghdad
5 WORDTAG O businessman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32607.500
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Heart
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Verstappen
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gasoline
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Andersson
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8-4
45 WORDTAG O hours
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ luxury
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ jeeps
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.43
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Faust
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_VERS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.92
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ humpback
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ demonstrations
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Times
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Paulus
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Highlights
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ collaborators
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ watched
13 WORDTAG O ROUND
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Championships
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fisheries
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ obscene
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grabowski
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ calmer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ season-high
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Provision
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Falls
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ packers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stemming
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Appeals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Repatriation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ thumbnail
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jet
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ T_RARE_SS
13 WORDTAG O 6-
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Cup
17 WORDTAG O looked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 829
1 WORDTAG I-PER Park
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Adnan
51 WORDTAG O miles
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 941-434319
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pakistan
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Coughlan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ deadline
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ AVIA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aviation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Todor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stock-trade
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 63,913
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1932
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ limping
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .571
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 301
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Neuchatel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Estimates
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ETA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zinc
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ W125
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Empoli
12 WORDTAG O cattle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ casting
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
55 WORDTAG O opposition
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cofinec
1 WORDTAG O Bank
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ bowel
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vladikavkaz
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pullouts
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 128.6
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ihlas
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Droits
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 41no
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ BLACK
35 WORDTAG O champions
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PBR
5 WORDTAG I-ORG IMED
13 WORDTAG O unable
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bose
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Frana
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jansher
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ consent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 918,288
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1/32
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15.5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ FREETOWN
4 WORDTAG I-ORG DE
5 WORDTAG O settlements
5 WORDTAG O Q2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,294.5
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ collateral
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kleinova
24 WORDTAG O step
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Highland
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Overmars
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
48 WORDTAG O several
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ finances
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ blackmailed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ description
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dariusz
1 WORDTAG I-MISC convention
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ forfeiting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15-month
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pitching
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Saskatchewan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ earth-shattering
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grabowksi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.26
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ censorship
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ringing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +5.2
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sammer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 320
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Purdue
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Englishman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 60,960
9 WORDTAG O stable
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Toronto
37 WORDTAG O 9.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BANGLADESH
65 WORDTAG O league
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ correspondents
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8,400
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ favourtism
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ valid
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30.9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Covas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Campaign
11 WORDTAG O feet
7 WORDTAG O shots
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oscar
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ skins
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ INTERVIEW-T&N
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1982
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bremen
5 WORDTAG O Seven
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boston
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Seeing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lb-1
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ slumping
5 WORDTAG O shelling
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Frechette
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Goschen
4 WORDTAG I-LOC .
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ conceded
5 WORDTAG O producers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6603377
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Greste
18 WORDTAG O debt
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sack
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bedi
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10.14
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ THREAT
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ N_RARE_
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Valdo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Theodore
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Forget
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 586
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 274
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Krejner
1 WORDTAG I-PER N.J.
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ proceeding
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ jumping
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ veterans
6 WORDTAG O terrorist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sternly
5 WORDTAG I-PER Boer
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cty
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chihuahua
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Princes
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ K
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5432
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stores
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Opava
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-1-47-2
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ inconclusive
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3.27
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ behave
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Edgbaston
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
7 WORDTAG I-LOC JAKARTA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 13.1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ AMRO
10 WORDTAG O provincial
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Torrence
3390 WORDTAG O in
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ GAK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Angeli
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marcin
15 WORDTAG O State
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ WINNERS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ knock-on
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ nationalists
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Carlo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ highest-ranked
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ANSA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shouting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Srpska
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cordon
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
11 WORDTAG O improve
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ technicalities
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ repurchase
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Globo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Down
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Richardt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ umbrella
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3024.95
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 705M
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 57.345
16 WORDTAG O common
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ letdowns
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ managerless
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ qualify
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ monopoly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sixth-ranked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guillen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ distributor
81 WORDTAG O season
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ballesteros
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ rapist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Louise
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Amr
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 111.50
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ approaching
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ quarter-final
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nb-13
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-1/8
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ fertiliser
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ mosque
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vass
5 WORDTAG O re-election
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ meditate
26 WORDTAG O keep
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guivarch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Butare
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .589
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ commerce
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PRAECIP
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ conductor
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Impala
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ accusation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ color
6 WORDTAG O engineering
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ proven
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Atlas
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stockholm
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ soothed
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ pray
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Riedle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Amaro
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Olympiakos
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tenor
37 WORDTAG O ---
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ enable
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ S.AFRICAN
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ukrainian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tier
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Athens
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kikinda
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Poudels
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Selection
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 24.50
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ lawsuits
5 WORDTAG O sealed
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Karem
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ relative
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tanjug
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gatera
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ flatly
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wreh
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ clouds
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ relating
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Flamurtari
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ suppose
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HEERENVEEN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SHEFFIELD
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MUZAFFARABAD
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ promise
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ swimmer
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ reflecting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dawn
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ comprehensive
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ pool
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ profitability
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ police-run
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ door
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Course
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Karsten
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Studies
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ economist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1978
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Salah
27 WORDTAG O levels
76 WORDTAG O party
13 WORDTAG O numbers
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32-year-old
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Indies
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ cells
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ smugglers
18 WORDTAG O doing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vowing
14 WORDTAG O activity
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ speeding
9 WORDTAG O hitting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Juliana
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mobilised
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5.83
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mob
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesia
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Labour
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ escaping
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ accounted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sep.96
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6-273
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pavilion
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Scifo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scandals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Belinda
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Griffiths
5 WORDTAG O intends
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 374
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ leaked
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Richey
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ acquittal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ battered
8 WORDTAG O Her
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ germ
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Seychelles
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ lawmakers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ genetic
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bournemouth
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ grown
51 WORDTAG O drawn
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ EEC
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ loyal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sheets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Giampaolo
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ assemblies
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Capacity
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ A.L.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ campaigns
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sutton
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ models
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Morgan
27 WORDTAG O making
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mainframe
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cremonese
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Top
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ spectators
23 WORDTAG O armed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ green-and-yellow
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ harvest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bogus
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ avoiding
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Renshaw
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ divisional
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ZDF
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Scandal
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wood
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ arranger
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ probing
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 204.74
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nephew
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ recomposed
7 WORDTAG I-MISC GRAND
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38.1
43 WORDTAG O agreement
15 WORDTAG O rugby
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stances
143 WORDTAG O could
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yuuchi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SURE
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 41st
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ complain
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ densely-populated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ben-Elissar
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Caddick
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ondruska
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Astrue
42 WORDTAG O away
1 WORDTAG I-PER Florence
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ RE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nazism
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pellumbi
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Canonica
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fair
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ directs
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Communist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ compile
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ anti-nuclear
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
6 WORDTAG O dn
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Richter
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ROMANIAN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ interfere
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Xenos
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ quotes
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ designed
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rita
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 60.33
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ hundred
10 WORDTAG O additional
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ups
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jacobs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reasserting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Accountant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15,704.3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marushko
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 850
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30,300-30,400
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dismantle
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +20
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gangland-style
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KM
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ H_RARE_PES
25 WORDTAG O problem
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wollek
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ volleyed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ locals
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Miss
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Scorer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reclamation
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9221-5685192
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gases
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ maintains
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dunnes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ overbought
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PAO
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aime
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bombay
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jodie
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Joakim
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ street-level
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ garishly-coloured
4 WORDTAG I-PER Taylor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 270
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ roadblocks
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Habibullah
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Twenty-five
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ahronoth
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ earthquake
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1003
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ run-scoring
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ spun
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ blew
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ liberated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 231-7
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ telephones
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cap
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ b-2
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ specialist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Director-General
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ fill
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ APARTHEID
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Universities
3 WORDTAG O interior
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ seventh-seeded
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ repatriate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 133.82
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20.19
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ minors
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ McCullough
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ IMF-sponsored
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Control
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Curtis
40 WORDTAG O c
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Akashi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +41
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2065.260
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-80
15 WORDTAG O either
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BBB+
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cordova
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Austria
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ plugs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ langage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ murderers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 61.45
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5.35
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ ways
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ heirs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aqaba
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 73-3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ absorption
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,074
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 861723
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 100=1990
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ m;+21.5yr
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tanui
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ culled
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Masters
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Orii
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ apparel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ brother-in-law
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CAMPAIGN
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Super
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 22/96
12 WORDTAG O 79
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8716
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nagatsuka
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bernama
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ contenders
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Capelle
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ handover
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kafawin
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ exhaustion
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Klimis
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ poking
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jean-Michel
43 WORDTAG O plans
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Veliko
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PRESSURE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ prisoner
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rutter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Perugia
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ founder
19 WORDTAG O sign
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2-1/2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_il
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ intense
53 WORDTAG O agreed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ F_RARE_CUS-News
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ elder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bayesa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ niggled
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Confederacy
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dubnica
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sound
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mistake
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ foot-long
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Newmarket
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Venture
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stiajkina
6 WORDTAG O operator
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ drive-through
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shockwave
35 WORDTAG O overs
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Laca
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12,201.09
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ scrap
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ criticism
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ boosting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14.5-16.5
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
5 WORDTAG O Only
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ atrocities
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
12 WORDTAG O income
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sympathises
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Basque
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TE
1 WORDTAG O Mother
1 WORDTAG I-ORG is
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Filip
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ damaged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ EARLY
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dunfermline
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Corcoran
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Brumm
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Military
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ukraina
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ deployment
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dressing-room
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Reconciliation
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ litigation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Joining
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ substantially
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ pesos
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fire-related
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Promo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inderfurth
21 WORDTAG O sector
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pakistnn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ McNulty
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ thorough
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ patrol
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Missionary
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Palace
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shelling
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hovercrafts
8 WORDTAG O treated
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ assessed
10 WORDTAG O 3,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nearest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ecumenical
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Red
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ spirit
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ differs
7 WORDTAG O grenades
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tremila
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ DECATUR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pietro
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 556.19
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Auckland
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Futures
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mahanama
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 408-8750
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 36.5
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ succeeded
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ pledge
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oman
5 WORDTAG O dozens
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
18 WORDTAG O range
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ broken-bat
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32.8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Espanol
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ observed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ al-Qidra
6 WORDTAG O highest
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Drug
8 WORDTAG O construction
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-116
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bart
14 WORDTAG O seeking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3:33.94
1 WORDTAG I-LOC W.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ protecting
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ .473
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fifth-stage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mid-East
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 285-6
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Italo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ indecisive
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ lone
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zairean
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dacia
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ hectares
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dayana
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Khemais
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ brokerage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ treble
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ro
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 44.78
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16-18
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pan-Turkism
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stamp
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Alberta
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Council
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ targeted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Overseas
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
17 WORDTAG O output
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.8584
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Demand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ WELC_RARE_MES
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ +0.05
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +168,130
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Manne
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:16.141
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tuscany
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ corps
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Santapaola
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ treat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.20
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Apex
291 WORDTAG O out
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UP-AND-C_RARE_MERS
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Faldo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ insurgency
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7th
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Holon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Culpepper
5 WORDTAG O 1999
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bankers
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Baltika
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Siegl
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ luck
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ liberal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ASK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mercken
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cracked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 04/06/96
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Perth
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ enclosure
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ WSC-India
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sergeant
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ respectively
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Edison
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stretchered
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Goinxha
34 WORDTAG O planned
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zarak
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ rallying
12 WORDTAG O progress
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ commandos
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 21st
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Radka
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ objections
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cowan
5 WORDTAG O bush
8 WORDTAG O 160
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Franz
57 WORDTAG O cents
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ obtain
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Clydebank
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Clerck
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ hopefully
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Eilts
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kombouare
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hyderabad
16 WORDTAG O programme
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MG-Technogym
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ineligible
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stride
368 WORDTAG O been
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nirmal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ self-styled
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ YANKEES
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ repair
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ councils
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ implemented
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ screen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sweating
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ eighteen
389 WORDTAG O but
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 413
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rosario
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wound
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
8 WORDTAG O wrist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sellberg
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 560
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 11,346,000
5 WORDTAG O searched
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sawn-off
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jul-18.Jul
9 WORDTAG O consumers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Llaneras
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_verall
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rain-curtailed
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:21.009
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14.8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ restraining
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ eighth-ranked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cullen
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dr.
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ umpires
1 WORDTAG O Best
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ overshoot
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ flanker
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ IN-NAZZJON
10 WORDTAG O pitch
9 WORDTAG O fine
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 99.9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hudson
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .602
25 WORDTAG O full
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scrutinise
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 22,877
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Telfer
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ welcoming
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Biblical
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.343
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ anybody
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ satisfying
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scuffled
7 WORDTAG O hot
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TELFER
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ clothes
29 WORDTAG O action
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Telecommunications
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 143.7
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 138.643
9 WORDTAG O let
8 WORDTAG O slipped
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ outfielder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Liberte
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Galatasaray
10 WORDTAG O begun
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LUSAKA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mbeki
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 941-8100
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ misappropriating
6 WORDTAG O beating
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ precise
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 61.2
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ alloy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Optics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ anti-aircraft
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sellers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Surinamese
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Brenner
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ tool
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ above-average
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Spurred
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.83
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Estudiantes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 25.
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ camera
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ woe
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Call
12 WORDTAG O sheep
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rare
6 WORDTAG O crop
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ symphonies
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-0-15-0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ revulsion
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 520
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_rd
105 WORDTAG O statement
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PRACTICE
26 WORDTAG O senior
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ informant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lob
6 WORDTAG O motion
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ANCHORAGE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CEDAR
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ MANILA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guofang
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ currrent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KinderCare
6 WORDTAG O intent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ El-Watan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bred
51 WORDTAG O refugees
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 962
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pipe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ leftist-led
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ squandered
31 WORDTAG O forced
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-3/4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ insight
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ shareholder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hyper-inflationary
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 13.65
92 WORDTAG O any
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ servicing
137 WORDTAG O We
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ +3.6
31 WORDTAG O opening
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ lasagna
9 WORDTAG O three-game
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ engaged
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Felicia
6 WORDTAG O bids
16 WORDTAG O YR
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ambitions
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Belem
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2/3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tankage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ adrenalin
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ phone
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ journeyed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Quinn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Messages
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ consolidate
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Hong
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Piper
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ justified
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ undertaking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Help-wanted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nine-month
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.4779
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hungry
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ FFK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lifejackets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 568
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-263
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ southwestern
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ zero
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ afterwards
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 13:12
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ilian
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Swift
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grasshopper
12 WORDTAG O spending
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ dominant
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc.
10 WORDTAG O B
28 WORDTAG O analysts
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Teemu
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gorini
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Huddart
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ pairs
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 869.3
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Catholics
44 WORDTAG O higher
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Peace
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicester
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ genes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 36,5
34 WORDTAG O 59
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MIT
18 WORDTAG O truck
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brush
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1663/96
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ athletic
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Disease
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TREATY
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:50.980
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pauline
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ oversubscribed
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Teravainen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 49.0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rawandouz
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ballanger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Beachcomber
7 WORDTAG O else
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_bligation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,156.79
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ vessels
18 WORDTAG O jail
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SMICER
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ partisan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nahar
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Loxley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Afghans
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vague
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ GM
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 61.64
199 WORDTAG O told
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Romero
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bratislava
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ GACETA
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Commonwealth
121 WORDTAG O Minister
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MOZAMBIQUE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Montenegro
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ succeed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Product
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ GROBBELAAR
11 WORDTAG O training
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Okinawa
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ai
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Husqvarna
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Baumann
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ First-place
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ probability
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lakelands
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Budget
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4,900
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ outdoor
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ gluten
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ collar
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dekker
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extracts
57 WORDTAG O race
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ battles
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 23.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 119.49
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ blanks
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6mo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Thou
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1946
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CHALLENGE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ quicken
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4,534,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CAN
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hillary
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Patrice
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ passers
6 WORDTAG O 170
525 WORDTAG O be
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 368-7
8 WORDTAG O try
5 WORDTAG O links
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Blanco
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Petroleums
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ dating
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yorker
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Microfiche
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Amrollah
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ creative
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15.72
6 WORDTAG O displayed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mandolina
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ prostitutes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ quashed
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
7 WORDTAG O 120
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2151
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ macroeconomic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ golden
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kournikova
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PREMIUM
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9002
5 WORDTAG O civilian
8 WORDTAG O happened
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ odds
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gagne
117 WORDTAG O four
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ shocking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Keter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 391-seat
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ capable
26 WORDTAG O One
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
21 WORDTAG O 36
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unavailable
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Angelica
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Erdei
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ C_RARE_NTRIBUTED
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 17.50
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ VODNI
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 71-57
17 WORDTAG O spokeswoman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rostislav
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-1-54-0
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ batting
24 WORDTAG O leg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ANP
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ sidelines
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ AMMAN
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 29th-ranked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ beheads
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 96/04
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kidnappers
9 WORDTAG O registered
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 221
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 156.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MOINES
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Rally
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ voice
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tirgoviste
8 WORDTAG O confident
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.60
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ frequent
9 WORDTAG I-PER Owens
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ W.C.
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Glickman
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ inhuman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14:49.81
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ forms
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Motherwell
12 WORDTAG O MATCH
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ levies
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ abetting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ possessors
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ frame
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ +6221
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jiul
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kamuzu
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
17 WORDTAG O leaving
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Falkirk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ flamboyant
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ solid
5 WORDTAG O realised
11 WORDTAG O living
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ barricaded
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Valuable
1 WORDTAG I-ORG self-rule
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ updated
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jan-April
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 450
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Padres
8 WORDTAG I-PER Masterkova
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ T-bill
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jyvaskyla
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zeneca
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 90.18
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:13.353
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-1/3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Houghton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Prize-winning
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ geared
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ eligibility
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ knack
9 WORDTAG O individual
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Brigade
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ misfortune
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vice-chairman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BATKIVSHCHYNA
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ SALE
5 WORDTAG O MOTOR
19 WORDTAG O 57
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MGR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Balochistan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ corrections
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 267
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sun
6 WORDTAG O expects
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ L_RARE_T
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rudyard
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ whatever
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ascertain
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:19.699
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ gunfire
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ degree
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Scunthorpe
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ jammed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 585
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ IAE-3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hailing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ garnered
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ correction
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ gunned
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ dry
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ BARCELONA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7,047,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 819.10
19 WORDTAG O saw
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2,400
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ telecom
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lock-out
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Barentsburg
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gopal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2:39.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pierog
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 146
6 WORDTAG O targets
9 WORDTAG O jump
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Zurich
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ understatement
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancashire
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fighter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ grey-haired
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ England-based
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ deferring
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ authentication
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ coincidental
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ monitor
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Senegalese
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CF_RARE_
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Finland
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 363
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ physicist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kulti
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ compulsory
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marken
33 WORDTAG O yet
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32nd
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cloete
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lokomotiva
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Neamt
2 WORDTAG O Team
23 WORDTAG O Played
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ross
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tribunal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sells
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ proportion
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.63
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ selecting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +34
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ shirt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Galo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Congressman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PAP
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Brno
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ soup
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SoCal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ expectation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ melting
8 WORDTAG O begins
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Quepos
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ribeiro
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Neil
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
9 WORDTAG O vehicles
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 97.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ warmed-over
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_pinion
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.30
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Disperse
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ demonstration
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ behaviour
5 WORDTAG O 398
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bentsen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.75
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nb-10
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Presov
5 WORDTAG O consulate
5 WORDTAG I-MISC ADRs
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lincoln
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shah
10 WORDTAG O separatists
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Hampshire
16 WORDTAG I-MISC WESTERN
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ derivatives@reuters.com
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ procure
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ SBPUs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unrepentant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Better-than-expected
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mpumulanga
8 WORDTAG O +3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KOMBOUARE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rika
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ bars
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Services
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ participation
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 448
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.35
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ zinfandel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Z
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stefanovic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bovary
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Manhattan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ father-of-three
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Siemiatkowski
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 937.891
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Partnership
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Radcliffe
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Amsterdam-Rotterdam-Antwerp
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lined
9 WORDTAG O carried
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ravenna
15 WORDTAG I-PER Mike
9 WORDTAG O mainly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wisdom
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ zinc
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Boland
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Empresa
11 WORDTAG O interests
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Servette
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Super
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 57.2
7 WORDTAG O Ambassador
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 357,000
30 WORDTAG I-LOC PARIS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extract
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 26TH
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LIFFE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mitsui
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .451
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6-1-23-2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pirates
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:51.960
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sterling
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ AL-WATAN
7 WORDTAG O fund
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ GEARING
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Krajina
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LANKADEEPA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9.050
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 21,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 42-3
63 WORDTAG O leader
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Supercoppa
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ peasants
5 WORDTAG O tries
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 290,000
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ thieves
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ consortium
4 WORDTAG I-LOC MONTREAL
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 63.87
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Realtors
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Madhumalla
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lansana
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,600
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ lagging
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ low-lying
1 WORDTAG I-ORG MILAN
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ uprooted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9-1-49-0
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ pick
25 WORDTAG O health
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ capitalisation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ thanking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ aylum
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ superior
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vegas
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10.06
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Krizan
2 WORDTAG I-ORG School
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Schnell
12 WORDTAG O minority
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ complaints
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sections
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ W195
687 WORDTAG O :
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ INT
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Miltiadis
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Posts
8 WORDTAG I-ORG II
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ deserves
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ motive
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Merrill
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.78
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 27.70
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Professor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vicomte
5 WORDTAG I-ORG PSG
18 WORDTAG O rounds
22 WORDTAG O young
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ publicists
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Concern
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ spotlight
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MEES
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +0.0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RAIN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maturity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Khandwa
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ warmup
5 WORDTAG O CALL
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ proclaimed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 206,464
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9:30
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ represents
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ textbooks
1 WORDTAG I-PER North
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Recent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ peasant
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 98.4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 81.64
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chuck
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,900
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ jam-packed
5 WORDTAG O Queen
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Helens
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ trawlers
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ preference
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Twenty
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tanzanian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 251/07
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Moussa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +0.9;+23.6
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Montserrat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Alastair
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dejan
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ LEAD
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Come
9 WORDTAG O stopped
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-7
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ abated
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ turning
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cruyff
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ electronics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 156,996
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Thai
5 WORDTAG I-MISC F
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ NAIROBI
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mortars
536 WORDTAG O not
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ well-wishers
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hershiser
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ collected
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ feat
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Assn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .444
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ jointly
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stephens
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Felix
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ non-working
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fla.
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ accepting
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Palmans
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SUZUKA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ three-pointer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marxist
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maynard
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 147.786
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wherever
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ notorious
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ demolishing
15 WORDTAG O property
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linford
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ depart
1 WORDTAG I-MISC First
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sardinia
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ relationship
5 WORDTAG O mining
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fans
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Executive
39 WORDTAG O nine
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nothstein
2 WORDTAG I-MISC 150
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jacques
25 WORDTAG O 58
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tutsi-dominated
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mamiit
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ non-seeded
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 37.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BOLD
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Manitoba
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Slavia
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
7 WORDTAG O continuing
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ INTEREST
6 WORDTAG I-PER King
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sinking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bulldozer
5 WORDTAG O 600,000
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 97.82
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Demel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shelters
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Boltfelag
6 WORDTAG O halt
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tikhomirov
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ disappearance
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 110.50
9 WORDTAG O department
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ casinos
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ STRIKE
260 WORDTAG O one
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dealers
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ preconditions
1 WORDTAG O Wheat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ contend
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 40-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ relish
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 756525
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ impressed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .356
17 WORDTAG O terms
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tchmil
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lacking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jardel
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ surprised
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ twin
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aperto
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
20 WORDTAG O become
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hoarse
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lynda
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fortunate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ exporters
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ accessible
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kaucuk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bekila
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ massacres
9 WORDTAG O allegedly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kostantin
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mir
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ screenwriter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dehaan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tanaki
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marek
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ newly-promoted
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Kashmir
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ broadcast
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 137
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jaffray
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .443
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mestiri
30 WORDTAG O point
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ AWAY
34 WORDTAG O production
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Havel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KICK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 19.99
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HIST_RARE_RIC
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ discussed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:26.467
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ heats
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lieutenant
17 WORDTAG O separatist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ BACK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Franco
12 WORDTAG O suspended
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dragomir
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Malgorzata
6 WORDTAG O related
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ preys
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Pakistani
13 WORDTAG I-ORG The
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Metals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hughes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ privatisation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ilke
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,044
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ influenced
18 WORDTAG O presidential
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bundesbank
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Little
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chandrika
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ principle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kappes
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ see-saw
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ honed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ DENVER
5 WORDTAG O Up
282 WORDTAG O last
9 WORDTAG O federation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gump
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ finalising
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Communications
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .439
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ quote
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 142.3
2 WORDTAG O National
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chiate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14-9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shattering
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ O'Donnell
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shipment
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lisbon
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Salamanca
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ underage
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cowdenbeath
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RULES-AFL
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Farm
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ censors
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sectoral
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kristina
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vicorp
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Abu
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PR_RARE_VS
15 WORDTAG O sought
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 312-983-7347--
180 WORDTAG O about
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tass
16 WORDTAG O job
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14,775,000
5 WORDTAG O TOTAL
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3/8
37 WORDTAG O seen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ripped
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ acquitted
346 WORDTAG O their
11 WORDTAG O cannot
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.16
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guerrouj
19 WORDTAG O 1,000
22 WORDTAG O 1992
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Anatoly
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ perfectly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RICA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 65M
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
7 WORDTAG O store
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yedioth
75 WORDTAG O minutes
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bakker
6 WORDTAG O surge
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ raped
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Batterby
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Illness
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0*
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chesapeake
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2-yr
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mid-tier
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extra-inning
6 WORDTAG O critics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ essentially
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ stick
20 WORDTAG O expect
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ want-ad
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pounded
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Crystal
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ spate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gimnasia-Jujuy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aryeh
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
18 WORDTAG O stated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2-141
12 WORDTAG O score
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ balloting
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ lawyers
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Museeuw
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grech
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ legend
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BABEL
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Walsh
930 WORDTAG O 3
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 525
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lahore
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ FSU
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Assistant
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ vigilance
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SLAM
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ FAIL
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Forsbrand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gray
20 WORDTAG O quiet
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Even
5 WORDTAG O prayer
23 WORDTAG O never
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shaky
6 WORDTAG O wo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ interviewed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lucas
15 WORDTAG O nothing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ minerals
5 WORDTAG O penalties
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ambulance
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ structured
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-0-24-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2,036
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Slater
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maybank
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vlore
12 WORDTAG O bit
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ male
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ admission
8 WORDTAG O room
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marcel
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ swings
11 WORDTAG O 15-10
7 WORDTAG I-PER Judith
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Martinelli
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ whale
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ E.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ emerges
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ muted
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vietnamese
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Misael
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 91.05
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hideaway
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stefaan
10 WORDTAG O vice
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unique
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ CME
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3.05
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ orthopedic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ na=not
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Weibring
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ .423
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stroud
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ importing
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Bundesliga
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ journals
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ all-rounder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1870
11 WORDTAG O monitors
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ No-one
2 WORDTAG O Investors
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aaxis
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ achievements
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ water-carrier
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ DRAWS
9 WORDTAG O 95
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 73.8
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.8
6 WORDTAG O amid
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ oversupply
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Warsaw
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nonetheless
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ meadow
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chaminda
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 35.0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Atteveld
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lietti
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7,138
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MATCHES
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ nature
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ personalities
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Veritas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tickets
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Whitlinger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ questioning
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ appeals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Burks
25 WORDTAG I-ORG OSCE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sectarian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Boeta
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Katowice
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Diniz
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Patrika
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oracle
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
13 WORDTAG O interview
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ sufficiently
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gerd
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 41.0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 300th
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Statement
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Khotin
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hancock
6 WORDTAG O maximum
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fowler
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ criticized
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ recognize
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Faroe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mid-twenties
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ghibellines
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:06.289
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hanson
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ same-day
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ debilitating
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ DIES
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32-
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 00.42
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hills
5 WORDTAG O barred
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-1-29-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ interrogations
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mecca
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7.77
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Working
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 32,900-33,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ offical
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 756
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ insists
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Main
28 WORDTAG O prison
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ interrupted
14 WORDTAG O introduced
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_UT-_RARE_F-S_RARE_RTS
27 WORDTAG O within
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 506
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LATTAKIA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ trace
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 273-5
18 WORDTAG O sources
11 WORDTAG O militants
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fourth-largest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wholesaler
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ motorcyle
17 WORDTAG O along
22 WORDTAG O tax
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ muster
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ medium-term
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SPRINTS
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ inability
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ++359-2
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ fundamentalist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rampage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ predicting
5 WORDTAG O 8520
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.59
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mineiro
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CNE
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ KUALA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vigorously
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rattled
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ dialogue
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Subpoenas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ week-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ disposing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7:47.78
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ one-kg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ play-offs
15 WORDTAG I-ORG COLORADO
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 75-100
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RUGBY
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 17.4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fixed-wing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ north-west
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ salute
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ annulled
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ corporates
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Klongprem
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .540
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ dystrophin
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2:29.34
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ encourage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ radioactive
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ centres
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Adriana
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ QUITO
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Azul
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ publicist
5 WORDTAG O stockpile
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Speak
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bastion
112 WORDTAG O five
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Zimbabwe
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tutsi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UDINESE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Etienne
6 WORDTAG O becoming
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shaun
3 WORDTAG I-LOC University
37 WORDTAG O working
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ so-called
9 WORDTAG I-ORG County
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ motorcycling
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14:58.29
5 WORDTAG O exiled
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 266.37
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 123.157
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Schneider
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hincapie
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pages
11 WORDTAG I-ORG )
6 WORDTAG O fails
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ appealed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ resorting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7:38.88
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.0822
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ McCurry
25 WORDTAG O continue
6 WORDTAG O offset
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Devon
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Nikkei
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Smets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3830.000
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.85
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nyman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ KB
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ substances
32 WORDTAG O If
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ undercover
7 WORDTAG O installed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inger
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ judiciary
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1937
5 WORDTAG I-PER Villeneuve
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.209
11 WORDTAG O protection
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahamas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10752.092
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Croix
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Talbott
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.10
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ TYPE
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gumy
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ selectors
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ recognition
125 WORDTAG O only
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 49,269
11 WORDTAG O doctors
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 33.0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lufung
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Equity
6 WORDTAG I-PER An
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ triumphant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dancing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20.43
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ motivated
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ variable
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Takht
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ carrier
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ left-field
2 WORDTAG I-ORG US
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Buddhist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9,500
22 WORDTAG O protest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 212-859-1610
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tougher
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 19999.777
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,453
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .453
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UPSTAGES
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cuthbert
7 WORDTAG I-LOC CAIRO
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ dissolve
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ amyotrophic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bailout
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ prescriptions
9 WORDTAG O SUMMARY
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 26-year-old
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Savicevic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unleashing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sicily
6 WORDTAG I-PER Takemura
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mentally
11 WORDTAG O status
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Whitehurst
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dahshour
5 WORDTAG O parent
6 WORDTAG O picture
17 WORDTAG O demanding
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ DNS
19 WORDTAG O bought
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sigurd
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Authorities
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scoured
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ chiefs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1990-95
5 WORDTAG O 599
48 WORDTAG O many
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ TOWN
6 WORDTAG O DATE
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ trln
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 67,000
9 WORDTAG I-PER Reagan
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cameraman
5 WORDTAG O pesetas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ disguise
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Robles
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ managerial
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cavity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Denham
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kilda
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ possession
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ satisfy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dal
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 37th
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ivorian
9 WORDTAG O Their
5 WORDTAG O laws
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ equitable
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ labourers
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Leverkusen
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Proleter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ inserted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 11.20:33
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlanta
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ASKED
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Patsy
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ signature
11 WORDTAG I-PER Wilson
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Schreuder
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 28-36C
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guantanamo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4X100
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6-0-23-0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .551
8 WORDTAG O difficulties
39 WORDTAG O growth
4 WORDTAG I-LOC MILAN
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RENNES
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ resource
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Women
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TRIBUTE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ teasing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Arguing
5 WORDTAG I-MISC GTR
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Goey
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ spell
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,100.7
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rinaldi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +7.1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unlike
10 WORDTAG O three-run
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ famished
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shaved
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bulge
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BankWatch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tricks
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ APT
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ hurts
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ attachment
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 532-8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stirring
30 WORDTAG O law
15 WORDTAG O hour
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ally
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20.036
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ seven-game
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ unemployment
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Acc
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:52.977
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2470.00
2 WORDTAG I-PER Charlton
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ steal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ PRAGUE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Casagrande
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-0-56-1
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sandstod
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6,746
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 29-6-64-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ portends
7 WORDTAG O versus
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ millfeed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cutout
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RESERVES
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ BJ
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 25-YEAR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cables
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 56rd
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ADV
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:21.715
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Poznan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cut-off-rate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ protestor
25 WORDTAG O wife
6 WORDTAG O 15-9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ deputies
11 WORDTAG O lawyer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ floater
15 WORDTAG O kidnapped
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kock
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Committee
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ N.C.
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ den
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Secondhand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ production-sharing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.10
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ windfall
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
15 WORDTAG O administration
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yayuk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guide
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .367
7 WORDTAG O failing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 28th-ranked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mister
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ sic
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Steffen
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ disgust
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Assembly
5 WORDTAG O attributable
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ petrol
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Caesarea
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rewritten
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Industries
61 WORDTAG O close
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ whitewash
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dole
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kumble
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aluminium
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Area
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.97
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stuer-Lauridsen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Meredith
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ghent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ expressions
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Luehrs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ averaged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ G_RARE_ALSC_RARE_RERS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Janette
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 101.80
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 242
14 WORDTAG O walk
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bonds
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ EgyptAir
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30.054
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ neutral
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tinsley
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mapei
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6,045,000.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4,300,000
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ protocol
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Margaret
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ronny
4 WORDTAG I-LOC 's
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SKHIRAT
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ overrun
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ weekends
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ slippage
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ earns
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unfriendly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Monza
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taylor
306 WORDTAG O its
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:19.762
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ CZECH
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ slash
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fleuchaus
5 WORDTAG O skilled
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ravanchi
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ TAX
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ones
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 65,345
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ installment
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ bowler
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kivu
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RIA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ moratorium
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ .10
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ allocate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Halle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-0-17-0
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dante
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 27.482
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ deliveries
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ metre
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ chartered
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ undressing
6 WORDTAG I-PER Michelle
8 WORDTAG O unc
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ precedent
5 WORDTAG O tell
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cables
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ castle
23 WORDTAG O investors
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fibers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.56
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Burnley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ repeal
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Malivai
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 'd
4 WORDTAG O Armed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ revelations
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Firearms
59 WORDTAG O lower
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hintsa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pro-war
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ NINE-M_RARE_NTH
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ dirt
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14-17
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8:17.94
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tempelhof
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Andrejez
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RAVANELLI
6 WORDTAG O ratio
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.98
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UPSTAGED
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-7
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ infrastructure
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ incomes
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Banespa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SLUMP
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 35M
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 226.859
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ migration
5 WORDTAG O shr
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ milligrams
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HEADBUTT
1 WORDTAG O SOUTH
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ credulity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dignify
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ six-party
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ constantly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 214.40
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mariano
5 WORDTAG I-PER Arnold
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Enchaine
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ depths
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gold
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Azocar
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ seven-hitter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-all
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sanitary
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fish
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zeng
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ AMT
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ unsure
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CPN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1994-95
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ jettisoning
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ raided
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Homeland
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Average
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Andruw
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Journalist
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.79
10 WORDTAG O effective
5 WORDTAG O pursue
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Al
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cede
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8720--
41 WORDTAG O north
97 WORDTAG O August
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.033
8 WORDTAG O accord
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kipkosgei
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Suleyman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Exploitation
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ offshore
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ peripheral
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Prior
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kingdome
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ memory
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ tolerance
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ intervene
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greens
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kohler
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 216
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ infiltration
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ekeus
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 120-103
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bonnet
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Langer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ brandished
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Parent
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ flooding
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 312
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30-year
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ blunder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 24.6
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ C_RARE_MMUNITY
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Christine
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ necessitate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ utterly
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PR_RARE_-S_RARE_CCER
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,196
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Valle
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jonzon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ B_RARE_SS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ spiral
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wiped
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Molata
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Minutka
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sebastien
40 WORDTAG O major
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ guidelines
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Man-of-the-Match
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ fresh
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7,149
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Niall
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ NTV
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.66
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Minorco
1 WORDTAG I-MISC against
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Brisbane
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aleix
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Edouard
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Irish
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Saboteurs
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ forints
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ coaching
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ DBRS
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ one-week
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ infrastructural
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Malin
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Subsidiaries
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ganguly
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ skipper
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Manaus
47 WORDTAG O 17
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ audacity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pouring
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Joao
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kwai
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 406
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frankie
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Daniele
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ove
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ municipality-in-exile
5 WORDTAG O 1980
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 87.5
5 WORDTAG O photographs
8 WORDTAG O prosecutors
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
9 WORDTAG O right-wing
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ outfit
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1931
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ gear
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +310.4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ravi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ right-hand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ivano-Frankivsk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.35
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ teen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Asselman
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ freeze
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3.5486
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ austerity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grandstand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mediate
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
11 WORDTAG O reserve
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Envoy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ divergent
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
10 WORDTAG O existing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ barns
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Strunz
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ tactics
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
70 WORDTAG O most
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Collectivisation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nemesis
7 WORDTAG O hog
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ arrival
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 28,716.8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inquiry
7 WORDTAG O avoided
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.75
19 WORDTAG O tender
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Without
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ .522
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ferrer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ vegetables
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ raid
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ two-out
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Naina
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ location
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Agir
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ mountainous
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ pre-season
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ insistent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RUSSIA
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ CRP
8 WORDTAG I-PER Iliescu
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Workers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ knife
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ meaningless
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ critic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rory
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ moments
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hesitancy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mercantile
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Individuals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Unaudited
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Soren
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ systematically
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ KARACHI
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 517-km
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ jokes
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ defiance
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.348
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cop
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ crowded
149 WORDTAG O before
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Possession
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ irregularly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SDV
17 WORDTAG I-ORG News
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oak
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Grieg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ obsession
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5:17
7 WORDTAG O staged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ climbs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ higher-than-average
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ upbeat
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pushpakumara
3 WORDTAG I-MISC GOLF
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HANOVER
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5,400
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SCOREBOARD-AUSTRALIA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15:11.40
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gert
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ conquered
11 WORDTAG O marks
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oliveira
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ AEI
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ problematic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ glaciers
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ missions
13 WORDTAG O unq
4 WORDTAG O Human
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 95.35
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aluminum
6 WORDTAG I-ORG SK
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Francisco
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ strides
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ depleted
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Serbia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ screened
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 310.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Croatians
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sergey
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cocoa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lambruschini
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HINCHCLIFFE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jockey
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Francois-Rene
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ warehousing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UGANDA
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Castilla
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hereford
2 WORDTAG I-MISC winners
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ three-term
6 WORDTAG O shared
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pires
1 WORDTAG O Daily
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNESOTA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Udugov
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-1-50-1
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wah
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ vine
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ suppliers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 52.53
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ duties
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ medium
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MULDER
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shipping
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dhahran
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.17
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 165
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 369.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gale
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LIBOR
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inez
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ persistently
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 23,000-strong
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ bookseller
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
17 WORDTAG O your
1 WORDTAG B-MISC East
10 WORDTAG O crash
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CRAWLEY
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Les
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 446-9
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vassiliy
20 WORDTAG O always
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ inmates
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Football
12 WORDTAG O daughter
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Dow
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sousa
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dies
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ commodities
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ autograph
11 WORDTAG O below
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 29.05
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15-3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ greet
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LARNACA
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bill
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SIX
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ultimate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gulyayeva
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ users
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guillermo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bribe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ beefed
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Missionaries
13 WORDTAG O However
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fraction
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 35-year-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1249-1286
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Batty
7 WORDTAG O facing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stronger-than-expected
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hover
5 WORDTAG O accusing
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ unearthed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Iberia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ROMANIA
106 WORDTAG O day
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ballpark
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ molest
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tonga
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ peacekeeping
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,113,785
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 361
10 WORDTAG I-LOC ATHENS
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ newly
3 WORDTAG B-MISC Grand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2370.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ separating
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Handrik
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hock
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ scam
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bidzos
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bulgarians
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Andria
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gauge
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Referring
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ courage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RELAY
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ sells
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.341
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Meghann
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ sixes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chalker
52 WORDTAG O going
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ aided
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ preliminaries
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Soufriere
9 WORDTAG O ballot
471 WORDTAG O after
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ waves
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ masked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chitauro
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.206
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sharman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ doubleheader
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ replacements
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jadida
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bodo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 41.
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Croat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yorkers
8 WORDTAG I-PER Mika
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ souls
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ coasted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mention
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6-205
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Leipzig
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:50.727
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hu
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38:42.333
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rudi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pro-rated
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ sensitive
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ diminutive
6 WORDTAG O 15.
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Today
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ perform
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 11
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Alomella
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ philosopher
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ near-ideal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ terror
52 WORDTAG O 73
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 18,867
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nudged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Geology
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ridiculous
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4,325-acre
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ ORIOLES
15 WORDTAG O invited
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lane
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14p
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ carburettor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 23.0yr
13 WORDTAG O ?
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 79-2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Caja
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ widened
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 18,174,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-200
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marx
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 611
19 WORDTAG O traffic
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ tensions
45 WORDTAG O weeks
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6-8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:14.784
6 WORDTAG O 86th
2 WORDTAG O West
6 WORDTAG O 33rd
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shigeki
18 WORDTAG O commission
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ man-of-the-match
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lacks
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rejection
6 WORDTAG O suspension
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hemmings
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lyngby
2 WORDTAG I-MISC People
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ attendants
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ flood
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Raul
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ year-earlier
2 WORDTAG B-MISC GRAND
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
21 WORDTAG O settlement
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 203.000
17 WORDTAG O attempt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cape
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ CJD
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ customary
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ dictatorship
21 WORDTAG O 34
6 WORDTAG O oppose
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-2-13-1
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Redgrave
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shipsales
7 WORDTAG I-PER Koerts
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stranraer
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ ice
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ judgment
24 WORDTAG O Result
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bench-clearing
9 WORDTAG O opponents
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Purefoods
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ commited
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bianchi
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pedestrian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ frustrating
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
5 WORDTAG O outcome
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ whisk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Syrian-Lebanese
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Belchatow
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ snatching
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ACC_RARE_UNT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Teixeira
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 107-12
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ consulates
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ sidelined
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guayana
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ secrets
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ utility
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ INJURED
10 WORDTAG O suit
3 WORDTAG O Workers
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ CB_RARE_T
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 119.3**
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ N.Y.
15 WORDTAG O Last
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rysich
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Institute
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ exceed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nb-4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wheaton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ forecaster
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ condemn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tramples
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sobering
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mirren
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ circulation
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Petersburg
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20M
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ marksmen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 357
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ fielder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.21
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Arendt
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ WED
6 WORDTAG O grounds
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ WesBanco
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Furyk
6 WORDTAG O inch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ individuals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:56.318
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ prosthesis
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aynaoui
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ fluctuations
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ appearing
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ apart
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 232
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ meatpacking
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Senegal
5 WORDTAG O END
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ransacked
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tromso
1 WORDTAG I-LOC WESTERN
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ needs
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 30-share
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ meditation
1 WORDTAG I-PER Windows
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ ALMERE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ discarding
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Greater
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 300-seat
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Berkrot
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2-15
9 WORDTAG O fellow
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Doorn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Non-Callable
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ shy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tianjin
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Stankov
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ prominence
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ proper
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tide
11 WORDTAG O alleged
5 WORDTAG O gives
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ occasionally
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 210,622
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Washington
5 WORDTAG O ARA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 37,000
7 WORDTAG O virus
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ searches
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 226-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20-minute
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +3.4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ferdinand
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ becalmed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RDR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zanini
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 13.26
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Schaller
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ f...
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
9 WORDTAG O example
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ longtime
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maenmuan
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lehman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ N'DJAMENA
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Carlsen
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Moscow
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ busy
63 WORDTAG I-LOC Israel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .Robbie
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Tennis
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ liquidated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.81
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ triggered
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ P.W.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:55.281
17 WORDTAG O husband
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Social
5 WORDTAG O trained
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Partly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Steady
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ straight-sets
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Manchester
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Stock
13 WORDTAG I-ORG First
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ parliamentarians
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 49,900
6 WORDTAG O relatively
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SCOTLAND
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cheuvreux
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hines
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Handgun
26 WORDTAG O tried
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ restive
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tyres
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Torpedo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kongsvinger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ descendants
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ quotations
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oeste
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shoulders
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Whiteman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hottest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5/1/98-02
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Challenge
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Breda
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gurusinha
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 81st
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 47.2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ privatized
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dollendorf
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Peltonen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reais
11 WORDTAG O tests
24 WORDTAG O stage
16 WORDTAG O finished
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RABN.CN
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 21,240
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tang
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ .545
8 WORDTAG I-PER Thompson
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ comparable
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ZAV
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ reshuffle
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Luo
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Web
5 WORDTAG O maintained
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Warhurst
6 WORDTAG O 180
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Babb
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Physicians
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ prompting
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 25th
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20s
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aa2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ half-century
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ SA
26 WORDTAG O inning
24 WORDTAG O paper
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sava
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Unless
2994 WORDTAG O a
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ waterway
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Anita
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Herald
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vinod
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrats
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ four-hour
10 WORDTAG O crashed
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ two-goal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Klerk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Snoozing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ chimed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Drawn
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Morinville
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Logistics
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 96.00
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Life
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 11-4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ familiar
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 202.90
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ brilliant
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 202.65
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ fixed
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ischinger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 68th
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lifeless
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Luton
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ demilitarised
5 WORDTAG O supported
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fees
8 WORDTAG O produced
10 WORDTAG O 37
9 WORDTAG O rural
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UIC
19 WORDTAG O allowing
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ gloom
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ accompany
11 WORDTAG O scandal
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Leyton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pierced
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Naval
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ contracting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ housewares
8 WORDTAG O places
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SHATOI
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ terminates
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5.1700
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cheveley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 110.4
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ spontaneous
23 WORDTAG O 32
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rodham
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ conman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shrinks
16 WORDTAG O vouch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 22.72
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38:34.682
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 48.86
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1963
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-3/4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bondholders
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Heng
314 WORDTAG O up
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ bird
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ disputed
2 WORDTAG I-MISC de
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Airways
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Poulenc
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zeyer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ GREER
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Aldi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pro-woman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lb-5
6 WORDTAG O arriving
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pohang
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ brain
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ratna
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Berkeley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 134
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,850-1,900
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 106.5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unfavoured
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Eliahu
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rodney
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rikl
10 WORDTAG O powers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vinko
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 43-year-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TRADE
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Confederation
21 WORDTAG I-LOC ENGLAND
4 WORDTAG O Hurricane
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Miron
9 WORDTAG O shipment
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 343-8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dondo
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ performances
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Voters
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15:07.57
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 186th-ranked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maribor
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Football
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ possessions
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dark
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wilander
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vaughn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ speculate
8 WORDTAG O became
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ teenage
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 51/96
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mette
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Harden
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Obilic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ arguing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ slotted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PP
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wild
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ adj
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hungary
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7:48.38
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ handled
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Miyaga
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lawton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ molested
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bearded
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chronic
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ holder
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ BARLEY
1 WORDTAG I-LOC 31
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Compared
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ surrendered
3 WORDTAG I-LOC LOUIS
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ legislative
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Edward
11 WORDTAG O draft
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MING
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ diets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Skidan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vidal-Quadras
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14,668,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reunification
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ AVAZ
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamils
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Weah
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ infections
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ northwestern
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.09
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 747s
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ irony
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 21,718
8 WORDTAG O SUMMARIES
20 WORDTAG O included
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Boavista
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12-3
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Iraqi
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Matthew
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sirnak
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pentagon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .623
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dissent
7 WORDTAG O 2001
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Catholic
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistani
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Isolated
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1060.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nikiforov
44 WORDTAG O vs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Osnabrueck
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ demolished
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Line
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ SUNDAY
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ machinegun
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Jamaica
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-35
5 WORDTAG O tested
7 WORDTAG O attacked
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +3.06
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ enforcers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 113.02
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ FALL
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ crashes
5 WORDTAG O caps
44 WORDTAG O 18
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BARUM
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ exchanger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ saluting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ routines
5 WORDTAG O bright
12 WORDTAG O moved
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Viacom
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ marginalised
8 WORDTAG O comments
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lamonts
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ FEATURE
13 WORDTAG O conflict
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Corsican
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ .528
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Keegan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ C_RARE_NT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ still-enslaved
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 66.74
5 WORDTAG O isolated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Regrettably
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ caves
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Olympiad
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 24-11
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 51,000
11 WORDTAG O airports
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ safer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Implied
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ licence
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lohani
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Roelofsen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ plying
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ CZK
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Symonds
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ clinch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cometra
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ exaggerate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sorrow
7 WORDTAG O **
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dispatch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 144.5
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ +358
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ conversion
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8,600
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chornomorets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extinguished
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Baresi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Thirteen
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ inflows
1 WORDTAG I-PER Poland
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cottage
20 WORDTAG O weapons
14 WORDTAG O unrest
9 WORDTAG O slow
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reducing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ C_RARE_MPETITIVE
17 WORDTAG O seek
7 WORDTAG O everything
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ singing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jyrki
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Premium
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MRI
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shipped
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ saint
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ willing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ toxic
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Roosevelt
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dispersed
8 WORDTAG O abortion
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bolton
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Donizetti
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1918
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ toured
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zanoli
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0:07
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ +0.1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Richmond-based
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kaiser
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ resident
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jewellers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ reopening
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Casey
5 WORDTAG O aggressive
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Armed
1 WORDTAG B-MISC World
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LOMBARDI
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tatyana
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ day-to-day
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7.40
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ PAULO
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SUB
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rationales
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ seven-year
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ DAKAR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Indusind
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ adjusted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ declining
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fritz
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1622
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Galina
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ convincing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ turnabout
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ editorials
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Segers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ subscription
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ mile
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ +11
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ swing
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ communism
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ semi-upright
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 251/02
5 WORDTAG O drivers
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ wild-card
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-68
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cindana
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ convenient
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Menlo
6 WORDTAG O 56th
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ geography
37 WORDTAG O PCT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Adelbert
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cultural
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Apr
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ booms
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jari
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ toughest
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7,961
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ administrator
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3.10
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 55-ball
20 WORDTAG O mark
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Economist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 58.94
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1=.6421
5 WORDTAG O camps
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vieira
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Continued
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ INDUSTRIAL
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Likhovtseva
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ relinquished
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ payout
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oksana
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ bishop
2 WORDTAG I-LOC and
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Acucar
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 143.60
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lynch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7.65
24 WORDTAG O according
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Greenock
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Amsterdam-Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lancet
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ denies
26 WORDTAG O services
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 18.50
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tramacchi
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Palmer
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 211
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chammari
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ al-
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Banking
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ irregular
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-31
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ line-up
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2,326.00
7 WORDTAG O labour
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extensions
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mitsotakis
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ confederate
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 25-year-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Supply
7 WORDTAG O faced
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ posting
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mother
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jacek
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ wholesale
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ implying
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ concepts
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ near-term
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ lbs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Commodity
6 WORDTAG O jewelry
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Testud
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ left-footed
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ officals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Silvia
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ EC
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ SATURDAY
8 WORDTAG O militia
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ .598
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Therapy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ brandishing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ drill
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1969
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ POLAND
14 WORDTAG I-ORG PITTSBURGH
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ self-confessed
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8.05
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ flourish
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Trevelyan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MARTINEZ
10 WORDTAG O advertising
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ramle
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chan
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ allocation
25 WORDTAG O centre
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bjorn
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Baader
8 WORDTAG O casualties
7 WORDTAG O 16.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ pushing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ requests
29 WORDTAG O level
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 112.1-113.4
8 WORDTAG O Amount
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Democrats
10 WORDTAG I-LOC UK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oujda
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ mini-state
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ illegally
5 WORDTAG O investments
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ touched
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ foil
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Third-seeded
23 WORDTAG O carrying
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 24.8
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.03
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Knowsley
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mironov
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ privately-operated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Harleysville
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ P.V.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ leasing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cast
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Criciuma
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_verseas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ziege
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dirk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ affiliated
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ NINTH
1 WORDTAG O Capital
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unpredictable
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Luigi
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Figures
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38:36.306
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HAVE
8 WORDTAG O capacity
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PAYING
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 235-6745
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3.75
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bhutto
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ tagged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ eager
6 WORDTAG O taxes
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Welspun
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesian
6 WORDTAG B-ORG FDP
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rousseau
6 WORDTAG O exile
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Los
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kalashnikov
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BioVest
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ districts
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shuffles
7 WORDTAG O decisions
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dutra
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9,306,000
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Reserve
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Taiwanese
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ loudness
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ drachmas
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Information
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ celebrated
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ liner
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Petroleo
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Zabrze
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ diver
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9.76
5 WORDTAG O [
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ reduction
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lloyds
5 WORDTAG O bases
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Simian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ schoolchildren
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tikhomirov-Maskhadov
5 WORDTAG O congress
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cheaper
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ville
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Omari
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ covers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ H&R
56 WORDTAG O issue
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlantic
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cruise
840 WORDTAG O with
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3-12
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ centers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ guests
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 60.66
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ BBC
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ surging
7 WORDTAG O Its
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lying
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MTH
8 WORDTAG O cotton
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Juergen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .454
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Junction
7 WORDTAG O possibly
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Istanbul
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ VERONA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38,915.87
6 WORDTAG O rider
7 WORDTAG O founded
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ sat
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ UNDERLYING
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Coordinate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ confronting
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ feedlot
5 WORDTAG O swimming
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ naturally
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Mr
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ thirsty
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ PAYMENTS
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cantons
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Leduc
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nagyova
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Arias
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kleiner
18 WORDTAG O dealer
7 WORDTAG O certainly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hotel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ stirred
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ aflatoxin
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ reaffirmed
6 WORDTAG O forecasts
5 WORDTAG O pace
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ alien-led
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ engineer
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Steeb
6 WORDTAG O signal
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ reject
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lb-11
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ intestines
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gouging
12 WORDTAG O whom
5 WORDTAG O BP
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ MW
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6,000
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fitzpatrick
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cetes
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Finns
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ envelopes
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ private-sector
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14,196
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12/01
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 359-2-84561
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tripped
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Suzuki
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ LAST-GASP
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Parrots
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3:33.77
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1.4788
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 190,000
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ hamstring
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ bone
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ destocking
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ primarily
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Madison
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pressing
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ transferred
6 WORDTAG O boosted
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Cimicchi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rousing
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Doctor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ great-granddaughter
6 WORDTAG O contribute
13 WORDTAG O industrial
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rushing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ billionaire
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4746
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ CATANIA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ end-year
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ holidays
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Battle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 44,525
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rice
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Awami
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Indra
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ applause
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ artificial
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
25 WORDTAG I-ORG PUK
5 WORDTAG O paedophile
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ hurry
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ semi-literate
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ equity
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10,760
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ insert
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ benevolent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38.11
9 WORDTAG O nearby
6 WORDTAG O compensation
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ LAGOS
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4.5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-for-5
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scrutiny
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ incessantly
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ adventurers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ courtroom
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +1.7;+22.0
8 WORDTAG O SCOREBOARD
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ modernist
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ profile
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Proceeds
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Antwerp
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ anti-Semitic
16 WORDTAG O passenger
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4-77
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10th-ranked
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wolf
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ AFF_RARE_RD
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ exploded
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ detain
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chonbuk
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ bureaucrats
6 WORDTAG O Summaries
9 WORDTAG I-PER Fred
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Semiconductor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ harder
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pignon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ enjoys
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ukyo
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oremans
13 WORDTAG O injuries
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Payne
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ curtain-raising
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ frees
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Impreza
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 14.78
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ currencies
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ unsustainable
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Arabs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ECONOMIC
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ FFT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .632
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Inderjit
14 WORDTAG O body
6 WORDTAG O love
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Secondary
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ submitted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,242.9
28 WORDTAG O how
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ No2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zimbabwean
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ JORNAL
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ +4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ writer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ duel
10 WORDTAG O barrels
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scream
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Given
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ tens
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ arise
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 1990
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ policed
1 WORDTAG I-ORG One
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Alina
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2158
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ offence
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .353
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ conclusively
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ series-clinching
20 WORDTAG O name
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ doubts
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Qiang
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 20-year-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12.19
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ deadpan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ gypsy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ establishes
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Independence
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ airmen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Colleter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ perennial
13 WORDTAG O purchase
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 12/09
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ long-distance
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Surrey
8 WORDTAG O definitely
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shield
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 05:30
30 WORDTAG O immediately
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
30 WORDTAG I-ORG CHICAGO
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ forensic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 48.2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ MONTGOMERY
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ rejoined
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ direction
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ banking
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wachtel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ super
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ erroneous
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Auchan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cabaret
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ secondary
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Actor
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ friendship
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Smiley
14 WORDTAG O auction
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ necessarily
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ wasteful
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sale
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tatran
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hopefully
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ combination
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ numerical
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Canberra
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Field
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kovacs
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ hoping
17 WORDTAG I-PER J.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ technically
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ROCK
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 22.42
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kouame
7 WORDTAG O partners
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-pound
12 WORDTAG O welfare
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ materialise
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2140.800
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-1/4
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1907
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ interested
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Markets
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Steels
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ consistent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lacklustre
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nachum
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ inspector
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Johnson
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ rescision
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ expense
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Honved
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ circle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ remedy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tadayuki
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ shortages
4 WORDTAG I-ORG TIMES
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hector
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.46
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ root
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ centre-right
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ solitary
17 WORDTAG O difficult
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 96.6
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chirchir
19 WORDTAG O governor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ clothing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nevus
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 58.92
29 WORDTAG O process
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Pointer
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hannover
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yuuichi
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Leah
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fujiwara
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sidor
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ counter
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Struggling
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ pen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ overdose
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ isolation
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 149
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chapman
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 38.50
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maigret
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ J_RARE_INS
8 WORDTAG O 30,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ top-seeded
7 WORDTAG O agenda
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rangarajan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 6.39
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ pension
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Prieto
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5522
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Belgrade
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Detective
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ anti-Mafia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Malchugina
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Recriminations
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ regimented
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ RAITH
1 WORDTAG B-MISC COUNTY
8 WORDTAG O gathering
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ unofficial
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lighting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-1
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Vogue
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ yard
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Durban
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Express
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ nepotism
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ carries
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hunger
1 WORDTAG O Social
6 WORDTAG O die
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ banners
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ emptied
5 WORDTAG O appearance
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ PEC
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ takeover
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jeffrey
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ online
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ long-on
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kit
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Coritiba
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ guidance
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kubilay
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ supervise
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Fedoruk
22 WORDTAG O These
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Maturing
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 7-
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ IF
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Brosius
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Lago
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Atlanta
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ indiscriminate
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Favourite
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ neighbour
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ tee
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1835
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Oy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 37.70
8 WORDTAG O keeping
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jacky
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 375.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ +8
1 WORDTAG O Research
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gerhard
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tacis
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ yeard
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ defense
9 WORDTAG O success
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ five-point
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ substitute
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Guard
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Barros
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ busiest
1 WORDTAG I-PER Polonia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hospitals
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ .592
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ trials
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ wrangle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Marzano
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ roared
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zadar
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Timisoara
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ McGeechan
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ academics
6 WORDTAG O pushed
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Avonex
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Understating
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ urged
64 WORDTAG O 67
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 8167
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ carpenter
561 WORDTAG O had
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Middle
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 26-57
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Shopkeepers
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Speech
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 25.10
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jian
38 WORDTAG O previous
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ BALANCE
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Claudio
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ fastball
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-session
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ujjain
12 WORDTAG O strategic
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ distribute
7 WORDTAG I-ORG TVM
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ rebound
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.35
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ longest
19 WORDTAG I-PER Meri
13 WORDTAG O thousands
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ operas
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Correia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1626
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10.03
19 WORDTAG O release
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 44.5
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 117.00
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ novelty
11 WORDTAG O university
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5-4
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ knowledge
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 127
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sportul
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5,122.084
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dechaume-Balleret
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
19 WORDTAG I-MISC A$
17 WORDTAG O polls
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ depreciation
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ QADISSIYA
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ting
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ undergone
6 WORDTAG O mm
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ supreme
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ cinnamon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 875,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Teguh
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Specia
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ logged
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Liwaya
6 WORDTAG O 32.0
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 0.08
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ superstores
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ detail
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Garlic
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 42-year-old
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 199,900
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ overreacted
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Dissident
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rohan
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 936.000
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ sovereignty
6 WORDTAG O monitoring
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Crafar
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Interacciones
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ TELEVISI_RARE_N
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ 9,000
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sochi
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pollock
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Zambia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wilkins
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Simmons
9 WORDTAG O disappointing
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ denounces
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Forschungsgruppe
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ lauds
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ decider
531 WORDTAG O were
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jiangsu
5 WORDTAG O intensive
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rwanda
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Endt
32 WORDTAG O interest
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ grows
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 4:06.80
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hovered
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ breakouts
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ NOVYE
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Wellman
124 WORDTAG O group
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gov't
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Anneke
5 WORDTAG I-PER Albert
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ scoreboard
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 11,450
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ massacre
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Hennady
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ overran
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ drinkers
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 447
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Highs
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Care
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ steeplechase
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ partnered
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ dizziness
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ elusive
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ soy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ hedge
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Jean-Louis
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2,901.48
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Griffey
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cleveland
8 WORDTAG O materials
17 WORDTAG I-ORG MINNESOTA
10 WORDTAG O 5,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ ringgit
7 WORDTAG O fair
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Rosenborg
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Chelny
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Spin-bowling
5 WORDTAG O selected
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ HAMBURG
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ extension
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ brains
65 WORDTAG O profit
2 WORDTAG O Army
5 WORDTAG O surgeon
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 43-man
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BBI-7.27
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Westner
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ collection
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Thiel
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ FORT
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Bobkova
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
10 WORDTAG O fear
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ carts
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 27.40
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Wouden
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1:50.858
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ _RARE_ut
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ injures
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Younnes
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 100.6
6 WORDTAG O located
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 2.15
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ Radical
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ position-squaring
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ kickoff
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ approached
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ showcased
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Houston
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ touch
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ SPEED
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Yulia
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ BULGARIA
8 WORDTAG I-MISC OF
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 662
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 131
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ contestant
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Heavy
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Nickel
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 100=1992
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 476/698
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ oust
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1-57
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Y_RARE_UR
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Gatting
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Versfeld
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 1,700
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 3,632.3
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Ojanen
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Videoton(*
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 22,980,000
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Sun-ho
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 10-0-59-1
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ reaches
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
127 WORDTAG O state
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Haarlem
4 WORDTAG _RARE_ Kuchma
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 101-member
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 58.98
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ Garcia
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ dried
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ 5,120
1 WORDTAG I-LOC &
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 15-4
2 WORDTAG _RARE_ 16.66
1 WORDTAG _RARE_ Tungky
3 WORDTAG _RARE_ 11,500
